const Data=[
    {
        Question : "1. Which one of the following river flows between Vindhyan and Satpura ranges?",
        Options : [ "1.Narmada",
            "2. Mahanadi",
            "3. Son",
            "4 Netravati"],
        Correct_answer : 1
    },
    {
        Question : "2. The Central Rice Research Station is situated in?",
        Options : ["1. Chennai",
            "2. Cuttack",
            "3. Bangalore",
            "4. Quilon"],
        Correct_answer : 2
    },
    {
        Question : "3, Who among the following wrote Sanskrit grammar?",
        Options : ["1. Kalidasa",
            "2, Charak",
            "3. Panini",
            "4. Aryabhatt"],
        Correct_answer : 3
    },
    {
        Question : "4. Which among the following headstreams meets the Ganges in last?",
        Options : ["1. Alaknanda",
        "2, Pindar",
        "3. Mandakini",
        "4. Bhagirathi"],
        Correct_answer : 4
    },
    {
        Question : "5. The metal whose salts are sensitive to light is?",
        Options : ["1. Zinc",
        "2, Silver",
        "3. Copper",
        "4. Bhagirathi"],
        Correct_answer : 4
    },
    {
        Question : "6. Which one of the following river flows between Vindhyan and Satpura ranges?",
        Options : [ "1.Narmada",
            "2. Mahanadi",
            "3. Son",
            "4 Netravati"],
        Correct_answer : 1
    },
    {
        Question : "7. The Central Rice Research Station is situated in?",
        Options : ["1. Chennai",
            "2. Cuttack",
            "3. Bangalore",
            "4. Quilon"],
        Correct_answer : 2
    },
    {
        Question : "8, Who among the following wrote Sanskrit grammar?",
        Options : ["1. Kalidasa",
            "2, Charak",
            "3. Panini",
            "4. Aryabhatt"],
        Correct_answer : 3
    },
    {
        Question : "9. The metal whose salts are sensitive to light is?",
        Options : ["1. Zinc",
        "2, Silver",
        "3. Copper",
        "4. Bhagirathi"],
        Correct_answer : 4
    },
    {
        Question : "10. The Central Rice Research Station is situated in?",
        Options : ["1. Chennai",
            "2. Cuttack",
            "3. Bangalore",
            "4. Quilon"],
        Correct_answer : 2
    },
]
export default Data;